[{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679122360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":13301,"timeElapsed":93041},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679126461,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4100,"timeElapsed":97142},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679135418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8956,"timeElapsed":106098},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679137108,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1690,"timeElapsed":107789},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":38301,"timeElapsed":146092},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679183352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":7940,"timeElapsed":154033},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679187009,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3657,"timeElapsed":157690},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4538,"timeElapsed":162230},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679197746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"76","question":"What is the piece of clothing you’ve owned for the longest time? Where is it from, what’s it like, and why have you kept it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6196,"timeElapsed":168427},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8049,"timeElapsed":177518},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679208768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":179449},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4371,"timeElapsed":183821},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679215088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1947,"timeElapsed":185769},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679217861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":2773,"timeElapsed":188542},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1266,"timeElapsed":189810},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679223027,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3897,"timeElapsed":193708},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225135,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2107,"timeElapsed":195816},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679228298,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3161,"timeElapsed":198979},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679230068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1769,"timeElapsed":200749},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679239363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":8386,"timeElapsed":210044},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1677,"timeElapsed":211721},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679242874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1833,"timeElapsed":213555},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679244072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1197,"timeElapsed":214753},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679247184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3112,"timeElapsed":217865},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679248484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1299,"timeElapsed":219165},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":2006,"timeElapsed":221172},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679252031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1539,"timeElapsed":222712},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679254056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2024,"timeElapsed":224737},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679260535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5436,"timeElapsed":231216},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679261950,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1414,"timeElapsed":232631},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679264596,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2645,"timeElapsed":235277},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679265658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1062,"timeElapsed":236339},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679268988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3329,"timeElapsed":239669},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679270035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1047,"timeElapsed":240716},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679272935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2899,"timeElapsed":243616},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679276034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3098,"timeElapsed":246715},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679278572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2538,"timeElapsed":249253},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679298538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":18937,"timeElapsed":269219},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679299893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1355,"timeElapsed":270574},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679303420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3525,"timeElapsed":274101},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2015,"timeElapsed":276116},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679307352,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":1916,"timeElapsed":278033},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679310047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2694,"timeElapsed":280728},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679313588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3541,"timeElapsed":284269},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679315681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2093,"timeElapsed":286362},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679319170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":3487,"timeElapsed":289851},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679329071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":9046,"timeElapsed":299752},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679330174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1102,"timeElapsed":300855},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679334004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3830,"timeElapsed":304685},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679334907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":903,"timeElapsed":305588},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679337181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2273,"timeElapsed":307862},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679339183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2001,"timeElapsed":309864},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679342295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3111,"timeElapsed":312976},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679344624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":315305},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679346690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"174","question":"Have you ever tried to cut your own hair? How did that work out?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2065,"timeElapsed":317371},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679353585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5828,"timeElapsed":324266},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679355110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1524,"timeElapsed":325791},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679357750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2640,"timeElapsed":328431},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679361010,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3259,"timeElapsed":331691},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679369619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":8608,"timeElapsed":340300},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679373164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3545,"timeElapsed":343845},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679376132,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2967,"timeElapsed":346813},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679380511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4378,"timeElapsed":351192},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679382576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2065,"timeElapsed":353257},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679385735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3158,"timeElapsed":356416},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680094446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":707764,"timeElapsed":1065127},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680097143,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":2696,"timeElapsed":1067824},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680099771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2628,"timeElapsed":1070452},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680100906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1134,"timeElapsed":1071587},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680103365,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2458,"timeElapsed":1074046},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680104665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":1300,"timeElapsed":1075346},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680106953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2287,"timeElapsed":1077633},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680109578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2625,"timeElapsed":1080259},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680111402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"49","question":"Do you believe in a God or higher power? Describe this belief (or why you do not).","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1823,"timeElapsed":1082083},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680118436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6288,"timeElapsed":1089117},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680119601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1164,"timeElapsed":1090282},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680120807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1205,"timeElapsed":1091488},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680121996,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1188,"timeElapsed":1092677},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680125270,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3274,"timeElapsed":1095951},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680126974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1703,"timeElapsed":1097655},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680128979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2004,"timeElapsed":1099660},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680130016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1036,"timeElapsed":1100697},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680131687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1671,"timeElapsed":1102368},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680395544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":263044,"timeElapsed":1366225},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680396661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1116,"timeElapsed":1367342},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680397758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1097,"timeElapsed":1368439},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680398807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1048,"timeElapsed":1369488},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680400899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2091,"timeElapsed":1371580},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680402377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1477,"timeElapsed":1373058},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680405633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3256,"timeElapsed":1376314},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680407637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":2003,"timeElapsed":1378318},{"subjectID":"4zb8d2sfny","prolificID":"650b695bf3b3d34f9c461926","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b45d323cb31f47f46ea","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735680409115,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1477,"timeElapsed":1379796}]